Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series IV: Governor
  - Sub-series D: 1982 Campaign
    - Publicity - Newspaper clippings
      - September 1983 (Box 204, Folder 17)
      - October 1983 (Box 204, Folder 18)
      - November 1983 (Box 204, Folder 19)
      - December 1983 (Box 204, Folder 20)
      - Undated (Box 204, Folder 21)
      - Photocopies (Box 204, Folder 22)
    - Publicity - Newspaper Clippings and News Releases - By Topic
      - Agriculture (Box 205, Folder 1)
      - Articles on Lamar Alexander (Box 205, Folder 2)
      - Articles on Honey Alexander (Box 205, Folder 3)
      - Articles by Alexander (Box 205, Folder 4)
      - Articles in magazines about Alexander (Box 205, Folder 5)
      - Awards (Box 205, Folder 6)
      - Balanced Budget Amendment (Box 205, Folder 7)
      - Biographies of Lamar and Honey Alexander (Box 205, Folder 8)
      - Black Community (Box 205, Folder 9)
      - Boys’ and Girls’ State, 1982 (Box 205, Folder 10)
      - Budget Address and Budget, February 1, 1982 (Box 205, Folder 11)
      - Business (Box 205, Folder 12)
      - 1982 Campaign (1 of 6) (Box 205, Folder 13)
      - 1982 Campaign (2 of 6) (Box 205, Folder 14)
      - 1982 Campaign (3 of 6) (Box 205, Folder 15)
      - 1982 Campaign (4 of 6) (Box 205, Folder 16)
      - 1982 Campaign (5 of 6) (Box 205, Folder 17)
      - 1982 Campaign (6 of 6) (Box 205, Folder 18)
    - Publicity - Newspaper Clippings and News Releases - By Topic
      - Cartoons (Box 206, Folder 1)
      - Corrections (Box 206, Folder 2)
      - Courts (Box 206, Folder 3)
      - Debates (Box 206, Folder 4)
      - Democrats (Box 206, Folder 5)
      - Economic and Community Development (Box 206, Folder 6)
      - Economic and Community Development Trip, November 1981 (Box 206, Folder 7)
      - Economic and Community Development Trip to Europe (Box 206, Folder 8)
      - Economics of the Campaign (Box 206, Folder 9)
      - Editorials (Box 206, Folder 10)
      - Education (Box 206, Folder 11)
      - Education - Governor’s Speech, January 22, 1982 (Box 206, Folder 12)
      - Endorsements (1 of 2) (Box 206, Folder 13)
      - Endorsements (2 of 2) (Box 206, Folder 14)
      - Energy (Box 206, Folder 15)
    - Publicity - Newspaper Clippings and News Releases - By Topic
      - Family and features (Box 207, Folder 1)
      - Gambling (Box 207, Folder 2)
      - Gas tax (Box 207, Folder 3)
      - Hazardous waste (Box 207, Folder 4)
      - Health Care (Box 207, Folder 5)
      - Higher education (Box 207, Folder 6)
      - 1982 Income tax (Box 207, Folder 7)
      - Interest rates (Box 207, Folder 8)
      - Knoxville Defense (Box 207, Folder 9)
      - Legal issues (Box 207, Folder 10)
      - Legislature (Box 207, Folder 11)
      - Mass transit (Box 207, Folder 12)
      - Medicaid (Box 207, Folder 13)
      - Memphis and the National Football League (Box 207, Folder 14)
      - News analysis (Box 207, Folder 15)
      - Platform issues (1 of 2) (Box 207, Folder 16)
      - Platform issues (2 of 2) (Box 207, Folder 17)
      - Politics (Box 207, Folder 18)
      - Polls (Box 207, Folder 19)
      - 1982 Primary (1 of 2) (Box 207, Folder 20)
      - 1982 Primary (2 of 2) (Box 207, Folder 21)
      - Productivity Study Team (Box 207, Folder 22)
      - Salary (Box 207, Folder 23)
      - Staff (Box 207, Folder 24)
      - State of the State, March 8, 1982 (Box 207, Folder 25)
      - Taxes (Box 207, Folder 26)
      - Tennessee State Employees Association - episode, June 18, 1982 (Box 207, Folder 27)
      - Transportation (Box 207, Folder 28)
      - Truck weights (Box 207, Folder 29)
      - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 207, Folder 30)
      - Vetoes (Box 207, Folder 31)
    - Publicity -Newspaper clippings - Other Subject Files
      - J. Pope Dyer (Box 208, Folder 1)
      - Hospital Corporation of America (Box 208, Folder 2)
      - Tennessee Presidents (Box 208, Folder 3)
      - Tourism in Tennessee (Box 208, Folder 4)
      - Trial of Ray Blanton (1 of 5) (Box 208, Folder 5)
      - Trial of Ray Blanton (2 of 5) (Box 208, Folder 6)
      - Trial of Ray Blanton (3 of 5) (Box 208, Folder 7)
      - Trial of Ray Blanton (4 of 5) (Box 208, Folder 8)
      - Trial of Ray Blanton (5 of 5) (Box 208, Folder 9)
      - Trial verdict of Ray Blanton (1 of 4) (Box 208, Folder 10)
      - Trial verdict of Ray Blanton (2 of 4) (Box 208, Folder 11)
      - Trial verdict of Ray Blanton (3 of 4) (Box 208, Folder 12)
      - Trial verdict of Ray Blanton (4 of 4) (Box 208, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - Opposition Files - Randy Tyree - Newspaper Clippings - Originals -Chronological
      - June 1982 (Box 209, Folder 1)
      - July 1982 (Box 209, Folder 2)
      - August 2, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 3)
      - August 3, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 4)
      - August 4, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - August 7, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 6)
      - August 8, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 7)
      - August 9, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 8)
      - August 10, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 9)
      - August 11, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 10)
      - August 17, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 11)
      - August 18, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 12)
      - August 19, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 13)
      - August 22, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 14)
      - August 24, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 15)
      - August 25, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 16)
      - August 26, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 17)
      - August 27, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 18)
      - August 28, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 19)
      - August 29, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 20)
      - August 30, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 21)
      - August 31, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 22)
      - September 1, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 23)
      - September 2, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 24)
      - September 3, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 25)
      - September 4, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 26)
      - September 5, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 27)
      - September 6, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 28)
      - September 7, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 29)
      - September 8, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 30)
      - September 9, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 31)
      - September 11, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 32)
      - September 12, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 33)
      - September 13, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 34)
      - September 14, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 35)
      - September 15, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 36)
      - September 16, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 37)
      - September 17, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 38)
      - September 18, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 39)
      - September 19, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 40)
      - September 21, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 41)
      - September 22, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 42)
      - September 23, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 43)
      - September 24, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 44)
      - September 25, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 45)
      - September 26, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 46)
      - September 27, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 47)
      - September 28, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 48)
      - September 29, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 49)
      - September 30, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 50)
      - October 1, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 51)
      - October 2, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 52)
      - October 3, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 53)
      - October 4, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 54)
      - October 5, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 55)
      - October 6, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 56)
      - October 7, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 57)
      - October 8, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 58)
      - October 10, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 59)
      - October 12, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 60)
      - October 14, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 61)
      - October 15, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 62)
      - October 17, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 63)
      - October 18, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 64)
      - October 19, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 65)
      - October 20, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 66)
      - October 21, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 67)
      - October 22, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 68)
      - October 23, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 69)
      - October 24, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 70)
      - October 25, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 71)
      - October 26, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 72)
      - October 27, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 73)
      - October 30, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 74)
      - October 31, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 75)
      - November 31, 1982 (Box 209, Folder 76)
      - Undated (Box 209, Folder 77)
    - Opposition files - Randy Tyree - Newspaper Clippings - By Topic
      - Annexation (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - Ceremonies (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - City Council (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - City Employees (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - City Finances (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - City Insurance (Box 210, Folder 6)
      - Death Penalty (Box 210, Folder 7)
      - Editorials (Box 210, Folder 8)
      - End of Year 1981 Report (Box 210, Folder 9)
      - Endorsements (Box 210, Folder 10)
      - Family (Box 210, Folder 11)
      - Fire Chief Paul Warwick (Box 210, Folder 12)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign (1 of 6) (Box 210, Folder 13)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign (2 of 6) (Box 210, Folder 14)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign (3 of 6) (Box 210, Folder 15)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign (4 of 6) (Box 210, Folder 16)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign (5 of 6) (Box 210, Folder 17)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign (6 of 6) (Box 210, Folder 18)
      - John Jay Hooker (Box 210, Folder 19)
      - Knoxville Police (Box 210, Folder 20)
      - Liquor (Box 210, Folder 21)
      - Post Primary, August 1982 (1 of 2) (Box 210, Folder 22)
      - Post Primary, August 1982 (2 of 2) (Box 210, Folder 23)
      - Post Primary, September 1982 (Box 210, Folder 24)
    - Opposition Files - Randy Tyree - Newspaper Clippings - By Topic
      - Post Primary, October 1982 (Box 211, Folder 1)
      - Post Primary, October, November 1982 (Box 211, Folder 2)
      - Press Aide Hiring (Box 211, Folder 3)
      - “Randy’s Rule” (Box 211, Folder 4)
      - Rapid Transit (Box 211, Folder 5)
      - Speeding drivers (Box 211, Folder 6)
      - Taxes (1 of 2) (Box 211, Folder 7)
      - Taxes (2 of 2) (Box 211, Folder 8)
      - Tennessee Municipal League/ New Federalism and others (Box 211, Folder 9)
      - University of Tennessee Arena (Box 211, Folder 10)
      - World’s Fair Knoxville (1 of 5) (Box 211, Folder 11)
      - World’s Fair Knoxville (2 of 5) (Box 211, Folder 12)
      - World’s Fair Knoxville (3 of 5) (Box 211, Folder 13)
      - World’s Fair Knoxville (4 of 5) (Box 211, Folder 14)
      - World’s Fair Knoxville (5 of 5) (Box 211, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous (1 of 3) (Box 211, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous (2 of 3) (Box 211, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous (3 of 3) (Box 211, Folder 18)
    - Opposition Files - Other candidates -Newspaper clippings
      - Annabelle Clement O’Brien (1 of 9) (Box 212, Folder 1)
      - Annabelle Clement O’Brien (2 of 9) (Box 212, Folder 2)
      - Annabelle Clement O’Brien (3 of 9) (Box 212, Folder 3)
      - Annabelle Clement O’Brien (4 of 9) (Box 212, Folder 4)
      - Annabelle Clement O’Brien (5 of 9) (Box 212, Folder 5)
      - Annabelle Clement O’Brien (6 of 9) (Box 212, Folder 6)
      - Annabelle Clement O’Brien (7 of 9) (Box 212, Folder 7)
      - Annabelle Clement O’Brien (8 of 9) (Box 212, Folder 8)
      - Annabelle Clement O’Brien (9 of 9) (Box 212, Folder 9)
      - Frank Cochran (1 of 3) (Box 212, Folder 10)
      - Frank Cochran (2 of 3) (Box 212, Folder 11)
      - Frank Cochran (3 of 3) (Box 212, Folder 12)
      - Bob Conger (Box 212, Folder 13)
      - Tom Henry (1 of 2) (Box 212, Folder 14)
      - Tom Henry (2 of 2) (Box 212, Folder 15)
      - John Love (1 of 2) (Box 212, Folder 16)
      - John Love (2 of 2) (Box 212, Folder 17)
      - Beard - Sasser Senate Race (1 of 3) (Box 212, Folder 18)
      - Beard - Sasser Senate Race (2 of 3) (Box 212, Folder 19)
      - Beard - Sasser Senate Race (3 of 3) (Box 212, Folder 20)
    - Opposition files - Newspaper Clippings
      - Congressional candidates (1 of 2) (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - Congressional candidates (2 of 2) (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - Other candidates (1 of 3) (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Other candidates (2 of 3) (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - Other candidates (3 of 3) (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - Democratic disunity in candidates (1 of 2) (Box 213, Folder 6)
      - Democratic disunity in candidates (2 of 2) (Box 213, Folder 7)
      - Democratic leadership (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - Opposition files – Other
      - Randy Tyree - general information (1 of 3) (Box 213, Folder 9)
      - Randy Tyree - general information (2 of 3) (Box 213, Folder 10)
      - Randy Tyree - general information (3 of 3) (Box 213, Folder 11)
      - Randy Tyree – disclosures (1 of 2) (Box 213, Folder 12)
      - Randy Tyree – disclosures (2 of 2) (Box 213, Folder 13)
      - Randy Tyree – disclosure, October 23, 1982 (Box 213, Folder 14)
      - Randy Tyree - Report of Receipts and Expenditures, July 27, 1982 (Box 213, Folder 15)
      - Jake Butcher - contributors (Box 213, Folder 16)
      - Fulton, Richard - contributors (Box 213, Folder 17)
      - Anna Belle Clement O’Brien - Financials, 1978 (Box 213, Folder 18)
    - County Records - Commissioners
      - Anderson (Box 214, Folder 1)
      - Bedford (Box 214, Folder 2)
      - Benton (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - Bledsoe (Box 214, Folder 4)
      - Blount (Box 214, Folder 5)
      - Bradley (Box 214, Folder 6)
      - Campbell (Box 214, Folder 7)
      - Cannon (Box 214, Folder 8)
      - Carroll (Box 214, Folder 9)
      - Carter (Box 214, Folder 10)
      - Cheatham (Box 214, Folder 11)
      - Chester (Box 214, Folder 12)
      - Claiborne (Box 214, Folder 13)
      - Clay (Box 214, Folder 14)
      - Cocke (Box 214, Folder 15)
      - Coffee (Box 214, Folder 16)
      - Crockett (Box 214, Folder 17)
      - Cumberland (Box 214, Folder 18)
      - Davidson (Box 214, Folder 19)
      - Decatur (Box 214, Folder 20)
      - DeKalb (Box 214, Folder 21)
      - Dickson (Box 214, Folder 22)
      - Dyer (Box 214, Folder 23)
      - Fayette (Box 214, Folder 24)
      - Fentress (Box 214, Folder 25)
      - Franklin (Box 214, Folder 26)
      - Gibson (Box 214, Folder 27)
      - Giles (Box 214, Folder 28)
      - Grainger (Box 214, Folder 29)
      - Greene (Box 214, Folder 30)
      - Grundy (Box 214, Folder 31)
      - Hamblen (Box 214, Folder 32)
      - Hamilton (Box 214, Folder 33)
      - Hancock (Box 214, Folder 34)
      - Hardeman (Box 214, Folder 35)
      - Hardin (Box 214, Folder 36)
      - Hawkins (Box 214, Folder 37)
      - Haywood (Box 214, Folder 38)
      - Henderson (Box 214, Folder 39)
      - Henry (Box 214, Folder 40)
      - Hickman (Box 214, Folder 41)
      - Houston (Box 214, Folder 42)
      - Humphreys (Box 214, Folder 43)
      - Jackson (Box 214, Folder 44)
      - Jefferson (Box 214, Folder 45)
      - Johnson (Box 214, Folder 46)
      - Knox (Box 214, Folder 47)
      - Lake (Box 214, Folder 48)
      - Lauderdale (Box 214, Folder 49)
      - Lawrence (Box 214, Folder 50)
      - Lewis (Box 214, Folder 51)
      - Lincoln (Box 214, Folder 52)
      - Loudon (Box 214, Folder 53)
      - Macon (Box 214, Folder 54)
      - Madison (Box 214, Folder 55)
      - Marion (Box 214, Folder 56)
      - Marshall (Box 214, Folder 57)
      - Maury (Box 214, Folder 58)
      - McMinn (Box 214, Folder 59)
      - McNairy (Box 214, Folder 60)
    - County Records - Commissioners
      - Meigs (Box 215, Folder 1)
      - Monroe (Box 215, Folder 2)
      - Montgomery (Box 215, Folder 3)
      - Moore (1 of 2) (Box 215, Folder 4)
      - Moore (2 of 2) (Box 215, Folder 5)
      - Obion (Box 215, Folder 6)
      - Overton (Box 215, Folder 7)
      - Perry (Box 215, Folder 8)
      - Pickett (Box 215, Folder 9)
      - Polk (Box 215, Folder 10)
      - Putnam (Box 215, Folder 11)
      - Rhea (Box 215, Folder 12)
      - Roane (Box 215, Folder 13)
      - Robertson (Box 215, Folder 14)
      - Rutherford (Box 215, Folder 15)
      - Scott (Box 215, Folder 16)
      - Sequatchie (Box 215, Folder 17)
      - Sevier (Box 215, Folder 18)
      - Shelby (Box 215, Folder 19)
      - Smith (Box 215, Folder 20)
      - Stewart (Box 215, Folder 21)
      - Sullivan (Box 215, Folder 22)
      - Sumner (Box 215, Folder 23)
      - Tipton (Box 215, Folder 24)
      - Trousdale (Box 215, Folder 25)
      - Van Buren (Box 215, Folder 26)
      - Unicoi (Box 215, Folder 27)
      - Union (Box 215, Folder 28)
      - Warren (Box 215, Folder 29)
      - Washington (Box 215, Folder 30)
      - Wayne (Box 215, Folder 31)
      - Weakley (Box 215, Folder 32)
      - White (Box 215, Folder 33)
      - Williamson (Box 215, Folder 34)
      - Wilson (Box 215, Folder 35)
    - Inauguration
      - 1983 Plan (Box 215, Folder 36)
      - Information packet with photographs (Box 215, Folder 37)
      - Reception for band leaders, January 14, 1983 (Box 215, Folder 38)
      - Tennessee Celebration - invitations, January 14, 1983 (Box 215, Folder 39)
      - Saturday Coffee and Lunch, January 15, 1983 (Box 215, Folder 40)
      - Invitations to Inauguration (Box 215, Folder 41)
      - Programs, January 15, 1983; schedule of activities (Box 215, Folder 42)
      - Address, January 15, 1983; Address January 20, 1979 (Box 215, Folder 43)
      - Cabinet Swearing-In, January 15, 1983 with biographies of cabinet members (Box 215, Folder 44)
      - Parade, January 15, 1983 (Box 215, Folder 45)
      - Balls - expenses, invitations, newspaper articles, correspondence, January 15, 1983 (Box 215, Folder 46)
    - Inauguration
      - Worship Service - programs, January 16, 1983 (Box 216, Folder 1)
      - Sunday Public Reception; Sunday Lunch for Family and 10 Tennesseans, January 16, 1983 (Box 216, Folder 2)
      - Communications, Security and Emergency Medical Operations – a plan by Joint Inaugural Committee, January 14 - 16, 1983, Drafts # 4 and 6 (Box 216, Folder 3)
      - Communications, Security and Emergency Medical Operations - a plan by Joint Inaugural Committee, January 14 - 16, 1983, Drafts # 7 and 8 (Box 216, Folder 4)
      - Committee Communications, Security, and EMS Subcommittee Reports - photographs, Legislative Plaza, Nashville (Box 216, Folder 5)
      - Ceremony Plans (Box 216, Folder 6)
      - Seating Plans (Box 216, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence - committee members (Box 216, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence - VIP (Box 216, Folder 9)
      - 3 letters to 10 Tennesseans (with biographies) (Box 216, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence - thank you’s (Box 216, Folder 11)
      - Event, 1983 (Box 216, Folder 12)
      - Memorabilia information (Box 216, Folder 13)
      - Facts about Presidential Inaugurations (Box 216, Folder 14)
      - News articles (1 of 3) (Box 216, Folder 15)
      - News articles (2 of 3) (Box 216, Folder 16)
      - News articles (3 of 3) (Box 216, Folder 17)
      - Press releases and other information (Box 216, Folder 18)
      - Press releases - originals (Box 216, Folder 19)
      - Press releases (Box 216, Folder 20)
      - Schedules, committee members (Box 216, Folder 21)
      - Transportation (Box 216, Folder 22)
      - List of printed materials (Box 216, Folder 23)
      - Tennessee Flag -memorabilia (Box 216, Folder 24)
      - Staff I.D. tags (Box 216, Folder 25)
      - Committee stationery and cards (Box 216, Folder 26)
    - Oversize materials
    - Removed to LA_Oversize
  - Sub-series E: Governor’s Papers
    - Administration –Appointments
      - Expirations and Appointment Dates –Boards (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - By County –Anderson-Cumberland, 1979-1987 (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - By County –Davidson, 1979-1987 (Box 217, Folder 3)
      - By County –Decatur-Hamblen, 1979-1987 (Box 217, Folder 4)
      - By County –Hamilton-Haywood, 1979-1987 (Box 217, Folder 5)
      - By County –Henderson-Lawrence, 1979-1987 (Box 217, Folder 6)
      - By County –Lewis-Moore, 1979-1987 (Box 217, Folder 7)
      - By County –Morgan-Sevier, 1979-1987 (Box 217, Folder 8)
      - By County –Shelby-Stewart, 1979-1987 (Box 217, Folder 9)
      - By County –Sullivan-Wilson, Out of State, 1979-1987 (Box 217, Folder 10)
      - Selection Process Binder (1 of 6) (Box 217, Folder 11)
      - Selection Process Binder (2 of 6) (Box 217, Folder 12)
      - Selection Process Binder (3 of 6) (Box 217, Folder 13)
      - Selection Process Binder (4 of 6) (Box 217, Folder 14)
      - Selection Process Binder (5 of 6) (Box 217, Folder 15)
      - Selection Process Binder (6 of 6) (Box 217, Folder 16)
    - Administration –Correspondence
      - Congratulations Letters, 1978 (1 of 2) (Box 218, Folder 1)
      - Congratulations Letters, 1978 (2 of 2) (Box 218, Folder 2)
      - Congratulations Letters, 1979 (1 of 2) (Box 218, Folder 3)
      - Congratulations Letters, 1979 (2 of 2) (Box 218, Folder 4)
      - Transition, December 1978 (Box 218, Folder 5)
      - Transition, January 1979 (Box 218, Folder 6)
      - Inauguration (Box 218, Folder 7)
      - January 1979 (Box 218, Folder 8)
      - February-March 1979 (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - Administration –Correspondence
      - April-December 1979 (Box 219, Folder 1)
      - Walk Across Tennessee –Picnic, July 1979 (Box 219, Folder 2)
      - 1980 (Box 219, Folder 3)
      - 1981 (Box 219, Folder 4)
      - 1982 (Box 219, Folder 5)
      - 1983 (Box 219, Folder 6)
      - 1984-1987 (Box 219, Folder 7)
      - Undated (Box 219, Folder 8)
      - Mrs. Flo Alexander [Mother], 1979-1983 (Box 219, Folder 9)
      - Mrs. Flo Alexander [Mother], 1983-1985 (Box 219, Folder 10)
      - Condolences on Death of Andy Alexander [Father], 1984 (Box 219, Folder 11)
      - William J. Carl, Jr. (Box 219, Folder 12)
      - Family (Box 219, Folder 13)
    - Administration –Correspondence
      - Alex Haley (Box 220, Folder 1)
      - Peter Jenkins (Box 220, Folder 2)
      - Judge John M. Wisdom, About (Box 220, Folder 3)
      - Christmas Gift Thank You Letters, December 1983 (Box 220, Folder 4)
      - Christmas Gift Thank You Letters, December 1986 (Box 220, Folder 5)
      - Special Letters A-C (Box 220, Folder 6)
      - Special Letters D-F (Box 220, Folder 7)
      - Special Letters G-I (Box 220, Folder 8)
      - Special Letters J-N (Box 220, Folder 9)
      - Special Letters O-R (Box 220, Folder 10)
      - Special Letters S-T (Box 220, Folder 11)
      - Special Letters U-Z (Box 220, Folder 12)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1978 (Box 220, Folder 13)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (1 of 17) (Box 220, Folder 14)
    - Administration –Correspondence
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (2 of 17) (Box 221, Folder 1)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (3 of 17) (Box 221, Folder 2)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (4 of 17) (Box 221, Folder 3)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (5 of 17) (Box 221, Folder 4)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (6 of 17) (Box 221, Folder 5)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (7 of 17) (Box 221, Folder 6)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (8 of 17) (Box 221, Folder 7)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (9 of 17) (Box 221, Folder 8)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (10 of 17) (Box 221, Folder 9)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (11 of 17) (Box 221, Folder 10)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (12 of 17) (Box 221, Folder 11)
    - Administration –Correspondence
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (13 of 17) (Box 222, Folder 1)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (14 of 17) (Box 222, Folder 2)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (15 of 17) (Box 222, Folder 3)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (16 of 17) (Box 222, Folder 4)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1979 (17 of 17) (Box 222, Folder 5)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1980 (1 of 14) (Box 222, Folder 6)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1980 (2 of 14) (Box 222, Folder 7)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1980 (3 of 14) (Box 222, Folder 8)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1980 (4 of 14) (Box 222, Folder 9)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1980 (5 of 14) (Box 222, Folder 10)
      - Incoming “C” Letters, 1980 (6 of 14) (Box 222, Folder 11)
    - Administration –Correspondence